Finding Aid for G. Mennen Williams Papers
Bentley Historical Library
- Visual Materials
  - Photographs
    - Ambassador to the Philippines
      - Office Ceremonies (Box 8-P)
      - Public Appearances, 2 folders (Box 8-P)
      - Farewell Ceremonies (Box 8-P)
      - Miscellaneous, 4 folders (Box 8-P)
      - Photocopies of newspaper photographs, March 27-April 16, 1969 (Box 8-P)
      - Album: Pamilinawen Lions Club of Illocos Norte, Philippines (Box 8-P)
    - Post-1966 activities (Michigan Supreme Court, Etc.)
      - With members of Craftsman's Lodge No. 531, F. and A.M. (Masons) (Box 8-P)
      - Formal Portraits as Member of the Supreme Court (Box 8-P)
      - Formal Portraits of the Supreme Court (Box 8-P)
      - Japanese Friendship Garden Dedication (Saginaw, MI) (Box 8-P)
    - Albums
      - Trenton Sportsmen's Club 10th Annual "Buffalo Banquet,", February 20, 1950 (Box 10-P)
      - Trenton Sportsmen's Club 11th Annual "Buffalo Banquet,", January 29, 1951 (Box 10-P)
      - King Paul and Queen Frederika of the Hellenes, Detroit (MI), November 1953 (Box 10-P)
      - Executive Committee of the 150th Anniversary of the May Revolution (U.S. Governor's Tour of Argentina and Brazil, 1960) (Box 10-P)
      - Scrapbook, "The Masons" (Volume B-292-1)
        (located at B-292-1)
    - Photographs on display in G. Mennen Williams Room of the Bentley Historical Library, all phases of his career
      - Adlai Stevenson campaign, 1956
        (left to right: unidentified, unidentified, G. Mennen Williams, Adlai Stevenson, unidentified, Sen. Pat McNamara, unidentified, unidentified)
      - Unidentified, Phil Hart, Neil Staebler, G. Mennen Williams.
      - Harry Truman and G. Mennen Williams. Autographed photo given to G. Mennen Williams.
      - Parade photo
        (left to right: G. Mennen Williams, Pres. Truman, unidentified, unidentified)
      - Campaign photo Senate campaign with constituent., 1966
      - Holland Tulip Festival, 1951
      - Mrs. G. Mennen Williams.
      - Ambassador to the Philippines, Mr. and Mrs. G. Mennen Williams greeting an unidentified person.
      - Family picture, Nancy, Gerry, G. Mennen Williams, ca. 1945
      - G. Mennen Williams in parade with baton accompanied by drum majorette
      - With Kenyan officials
        (left to right: American Consul General in Nairobi, Richard B. Freund, G. Mennen Williams, Minister of State for Constitutional Affairs and Economic Development, Mr. Jomo Kenyatta)
      - G. Mennen Williams and elephant (in Africa)
      - John F. Kennedy and G. Mennen Williams on a boat.
      - G. Mennen Williams and unidentified person.
      - Horace L. Sheffield, G. Mennen Williams, Martin Luther King, Jr.
      - G. Mennen Williams with Robert Kennedy (Attorney General), Ivory Coast Independence, August 6-7, 1961
      - G. Mennen Williams exiting a car
      - G. Mennen Williams making a speech
      - G. Mennen Williams inaugural
      - Family photograph
    - Color Transparencies
      The color transparencies are primarily images from travels in Europe, Israel, Africa, Asia, and South America. There are also images from Mackinac Island, hunting and fishing outings, and the Rose Bowl (1951?). Some identifications are tentative.
      - Liberia, 1958; 4 boxes (Box 11-P)
      - Europe, 1959
        - West and East Berlin (Box 11-P)
        - Warsaw (Box 11-P)
        - Athens (Box 11-P)
        - Rome (Box 11-P)
        - Krakow (Box 11-P)
      - Israel, 1959
        - Williams-Hart Forest (Box 11-P)
        - Passion Week (Box 11-P)
        - Bazaars (Box 11-P)
        - Temple Area (Box 11-P)
      - Puerto Rico, 1959; 2 boxes (Box 11-P)
      - South America, 1959
        - Rio de Janeiro (Box 11-P)
        - Buenos Aires/Codova (Box 11-P)
        - Montevideo (Box 11-P)
      - Africa
        - Ethiopia, 2 boxes (Box 11-P)
        - Rhodesia, 4 boxes (Box 11-P)
        - Angola, 5 boxes (Box 11-P)
        - Ivory Coast, 3 boxes (Box 11-P)
        - Congo, 2 boxes (Box 11-P)
        - Zanzibar/Uganda (Box 11-P)
        - High Commission Territories (Box 11-P)
      - Arizona (Box 11-P)
      - Hunting and Fishing (Box 11-P)
      - Mackinac Island, 2 boxes (Box 11-P)
      - Rose Bowl, 4 boxes (Box 11-P)
      - Tokyo/Hong Kong/Afghanistan/India, 3 boxes (Box 11-P)
  - Films
    The Films series includes campaign films and television advertisements, actuality footage, documentary footage of ceremonial events which Williams attended or took part in, footage of Williams appearances on television news programs, and several State Department and network television films on Africa, several of which Williams appeared in. This is a preliminary inventory to the films, some identifications are tentative. The arrangement of the inventory is basically chronological. Unless otherwise noted, films are 16mm, b/w, sound. Film numbers follow the description.
    The 16mm films were digitized in 2009 as part of film and video preservation project. A Beta SP master was made of each film along with high resolution digital files (mpeg2) of selected films and DVD and streaming files (flash) of each film. Several films are currently available online as streaming video. Other files can be mounted by request.
    - Governor
      - A Businessman Speaks for G. Mennen Williams, 1954 Campaign (3), [86393-1]
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:00:24
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-1, flv
      - A Veteran Speaks for G Mennen Williams, 1954 Campaign (4), [86393-2]
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:00:23
          [Restricted]
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-2, flv
      - A Housewife Speaks for G. Mennen Williams, 1954 Campaign (5), [86393-3]
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:00:25
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-3, flv
      - A Mother Speaks for G. Mennen Williams, 1954 Campaign (6), [86393-4]
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:00:23
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-4, flv
      - Caberfae Press Day 1955 (WWTV Newsfilm) (People skiing, Nancy Williams and Son Gerry at Banquet.) (11), 1955, [86393-5]
        (Photography by Charles Ray)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, silent, 00:05:05
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-5, flv
      - "Face the Nation,", April 10, 1955; [86393-6]
        (1955 telecast; assessment of the past election; discussion of the role of labor in the campaign; national issues;)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:28:42
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-6, flv
      - "Governor Williams address to 86th Michigan Legislature," (46), June 13, 1956; [86393-71-1]
        (Reel one of two.)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-7-1, flv
      - "Governor Williams address to 86th Michigan Legislature," (47), June 13, 1956; [86393-82-2]
        (Reel two of two.)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-8-2, flv
      - "Re-election Campaign Talk" (53), 1956; [86393-9]
        (Probably kinescope TV telecast; portions of display are blurry)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:14:32
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-9, flv
      - "Let's Stop Mass Unemployment" (54), September 28, 1956; [86393-10]
        (Probably kinescope television broadcast, somewhat blurry)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:14:22
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-10, flv
      - "What Happened to Our Roads" (Kinescope broadcast) (55), October 5, 1956; [86393-11]
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:14:35
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-11, flv
      - "The New Michigan--The New American," Political announcement (56), October 15, 1956; [86393-12]
        (Kinescope broadcast; fourth in a series of televised campaign talks)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:12:56
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-12, flv
      - Numerous Michigan buildings and locations, footage for campaign films (12), 1956; [86393-13]
        (Unemployment line, slums, poor roads, U-M buildings)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, silent, 00:09:44
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-13, flv
      - Democratic Party promotion film, (21), 1956; [86393-14]
        (Television spot with political jingle in the background)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:00:25
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-14, flv
      - Vice-President Richard Nixon (24), 1956; [86393-15]
        (Nixon campaigning in Michigan, including news conference)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:02:46
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-15, flv
      - Mackinac Bridge Dedication Ceremonies (23), 1957; [86393-16]
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, silent (Box 12-P)
        - Use Copy:, 3/4-inch and vhs tape (Box 13-P)
      - 1958 Campaign in Novi, Michigan. (19), 1958, [86393-17]
        - Original:, 8 mm film, color, silent (Box 12-P)
      - Governors' Conference on Civil Rights, Detroit, Michigan (20), January 30, 1959; [86393-18]
        (participants include Orville Freeman, Robert Meyner, G. Mennen Williams, the governor of Massachusetts, Indiana, Governor William Stratton of Illinois. The panel begins talking of taxes and budget.)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:07:34
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-18, flv
      - Governors' Conference on Civil Rights (D-9-A-65), January 30, 1959; [86393-19]
        (MSU president John Hannah speaks on the accomplishments of the Civil Rights Commission)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:03:53
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-19, flv
      - Cleveland Bar Association Speech (22), April 7, 1959; [86393-20]
        (Williams is interviewed about the past election)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, neg, optical, 00:03:47
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-20, flv
      - Untitled: (At Wayne State University and in Detroit) (48), undated; [86393-21]
        (undated; GMW viewing construction at WSU)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, silent, 00:01:53
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-21, flv
      - "I.S.D. Day," International Students' Day, Lansing, Michigan (49), ca. 1959-60, [86393-22]
        (undated (after 1958); brief message by GMW, then views of the conference center with voice-over describing the event; views of group touring automobile assembly line in Lansing; and of MSU farm implement center; tour of state capitol; GMW calling a square dance)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:15:55
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-22, flv
      - "Political Talk" (50), 1952
        (undated, 1952))
        - Original:, [86393-23]; 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:04:19
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-23, flv
      - "Political Spot" (51), 1952; [86393-24]
        (This is a duplicate of item no. 25)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:04:53
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-24, flv
      - "Governor Williams Program No. 1" (52), 1952; [86393-25]
        (This is a duplicate of item no. 24)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:04:46
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-25, flv
      - "Williams Tax" (D-9-A-44), circa 1955-1956; [86393-26]
        (undated, Williams at desk with Mayor Louis Mariani and another individual (Rep. Conlin ?))
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:02:44
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-26, flv
      - "Maile Veterans Trust Fund" (D-9-A-50), undated; [86393-27]
        (undated kinescope; non-GMW talk by individual opposed to Gov. Williams position on Veterans Trust Fund)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:01:23
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-27, flv
      - "Williams Tax Proposal" (D-9-A-64), undated; [86393-28]
        (undated; includes view of GMW and newsmen in TV studio, WWJ-TV)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:04:05
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-28, flv
      - "Governor Williams Taxes" (D-9-A-66), undated; [86393-29]
        (undated mid-1950s interview conducted by Ven Marshall)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:00:49
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-29, flv
      - "Mayor Agron" (D-9-B-1), undated; [86393-30]
        (undated; talk about relations between East and West)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:02:37
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-30, flv
      - "Governor Williams F.H.A. Plan" (D-9-B-26), undated; [86393-31]
        (undated; loans for industrial and research projects)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:01:12
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-31, flv
      - "Governor Williams" (D-9-C-73), undated; [86393-32]
        (undated; change in unemployment compensation laws; GMW speaks against Smeekens Bill)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:01:26
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-32, flv
      - "Governor Williams Tax Conference" (D-9-J-64), undated; [86393-33]
        (undated; speaks against Republican tax program)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:02:33
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-33, flv
      - "Williams" (D-9-J-69) (payroll Tax), undated; [86393-35]
        (Williams statement on signing of tax bills against his will
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:02:10
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-34, flv
      - "Williams" (D-9-K-68)
        (undated; payroll tax talk)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:00:55
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-35, flv
      - "Williams" (D-9-L-47)
        (undated;)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:01:16
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-36, flv
      - "Williams" (D-60-B-43), circa 1959; [86393-37]
        (undated, ca. 1959 interview with Ven Marshall about Michigan's tax situation)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:02:11
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-37, flv
      - Unidentified (D-9-L-64), 1959-60, [86393-38]
        (1959-60; New Year's Greeting)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:01:19
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-38, flv
    - Assistant Secretary of State for African Affairs
      - "Eyewitness to History: Black Star of Nkrumah" CBS News (copyright 1961) (83), November 10, 1961; [86393-39]
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:29:13
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-39, flv
      - "Educational Film": (Report to the People of Pennsylvania, Senators Joseph Clark and Hugh Scott, with Assistant Secretary of State for African Affairs, G. Mennen Williams), [86393-40]
        (undated ca. 1962-63 relating to the situation in the Congo.)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:28:36
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-40, flv
      - "A Time for Hope" (Documentary on African measles immunization program with introduction by G. Mennen Williams), [86393-41]
        (undated 1961-1963)
        - Original:, 16mm film, color, pos, optical, 00:19:33
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-41, flv
      - "Les Manifestations du 22 Septembre 1965" (G. Mennen Williams at Mali independence celebration), September 22, 1965; [86393-42]
        - Original:, 16mm film, color, optical (Box 12-P)
        - Use Copy:, 3/4-inch tape (Box 13-P)
      - Fifth Independence day celebration parade and reception, Bamako, Mali, September 22, 1965; [86393-43]
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, silent, 00:01:38
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-43, flv
      - G. Mennen Williams in Accra 1964 (Touring dam construction site with Leaders) (13), 1964, [86393-44]
        (Also includes arrival in city and diplomatic greetings)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, silent, 00:08:10
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-44, flv
      - G. Mennen Williams in Dakar 1964 (Touring construction with Leaders) (14), 1964, [86393-45]
        (Dakar 3: reviews and receptions; African dance)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, silent, 00:09:57
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 13)
        - Streaming File: 86393-45, flv
      - G. Mennen Williams in Accra (15), 1964; [86393-46]
        (on tour, greeting and visiting with young people, perhaps Peace Corps volunteers; also meeting with African youth)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, silent, 00:07:51
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 14)
        - Streaming File: 86393-46, flv
      - G. Mennen Williams in Dakar 1964 (with leaders, groups, speaking) (16), 1964, [86393-47]
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, silent, 00:07:54
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 14)
        - Streaming File: 86393-47, flv
      - G. Mennen Williams in Dakar 1964 (with leaders, groups, speaking) (17), 1964, [86393-48]
        (View of the city from the air; reception line; meeting young people; press conference)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, silent, 00:07:46
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 14)
        - Streaming File: 86393-48, flv
    - Senatorial Campaign, 1966
      - 1966 Senatorial Campaign Commercials, [86393-49]
        (13 Commercials (168 (duplicated number)))
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:11:07
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 14)
        - Streaming File: 86393-49, flv
      - Spots (8](1979 remake), [86393-52]
        (1966 campaign ads)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:06:29
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 14)
        - Streaming File: 86393-52, flv
      - G. Mennen Williams and Ted Kennedy (168 (duplicated number)), 1966; [86393-53]
        (undated 1966 GMW and Ted Kennedy speak in Flint, Michigan)
        - Original:, 16mm film, color, pos, mag, 00:09:13
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 14)
        - Streaming File: 86393-53, flv
      - "Teddy, (Kennedy] in Flint
        (undated 1966 Ted Kennedy speech, continuation of 86393-53; after speech, there is brief news conference and campaign posing; also TK campaign message for GMW)
        - Original:, 16mm film, color, pos, mag, 00:06:26
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 14)
        - Streaming File: 86393-54, flv
      - "Teddy," (Kennedy], 1966 undated; [86393-55]
        (another take of campaign message for GMW))
        - Original:, 16mm film, color, pos, mag, 00:01:07
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 14)
        - Streaming File: 86393-55, flv
      - "Teddy Kennedy"; (1966 Election spot for Williams], [86383-56]
        (either duplicate copy or a different take of TK campaign message)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:01:07
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 14)
        - Streaming File: 86393-56, flv
      - "Michigan Primary" ("The Milt Brown Show," Cavanagh-Williams Primary Race, NBC News), 1966; [86393-57]
        (undated 1966 views of the primary campaign; interviews with Cavanugh spokesmen; the voice-over and the closing remarks made by Aline Saarinen (probably for NBC))
        - Original:, 16mm film, color, pos, optical, 00:04:32
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 14)
        - Streaming File: 86393-57, flv
      - Senatorial Campaign 1966 President Lyndon Johnson speaks to voters on behalf of Democratic Party candidates. (17-1), 1966, [86393-58]
        (LBJ address to nation praising the 89th Congress; pre-election talk)
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:04:12
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 14)
        - Streaming File: 86393-58, flv
      - Senatorial Campaign 1966 G. Mennen Williams announces Senate candidacy. (17-2), 1966, [86393-59]
        - Original:, 16mm film, b/w, pos, optical, 00:01:42
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 14)
        - Streaming File: 86393-59, flv
      - Senatorial Campaign 1966 G. Mennen Williams campaigning at Oakland County Fair. (17-3), 1966, [86393-60]
        - Original:, 16mm film, color, pos, silent, 00:05:28
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 14)
        - Streaming File: 86393-60, flv
      - Senatorial Campaign 1966 G. Mennen Williams campaigning. Michigan State Fair. (17-4), 1966, [86393-61]
        - Original:, 16mm film, color, pos, silent, 00:02:30
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 14)
        - Streaming File: 86393-61, flv
      - "Williams interview at Airport (L6-7-7-117), July 1966; [86393-62]
        (Speaks briefly of his record as governor as opposed to George Romney)
        - Original:, 16mm film, color, pos, mag, 00:00:36
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 14)
        - Streaming File: 86393-62, flv
      - "Election Wrap-up Package, Williams wins" (G. Mennen Williams and Cavanagh speeches (L6-8-3-110), August 1966; [86393-63]
        (Cavanagh concession speech)
        - Original:, 16mm film, color, pos, mag, 00:03:24
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 14)
        - Streaming File: 86393-63, flv
      - "Williams interviewed about Kennedy Visit" (L6-8-22-39), August 1966; [86393-64]
        (Talks of various issues)
        - Original:, 16mm film, color, pos, mag, 00:01:10
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 14)
        - Streaming File: 86393-64, flv
      - "Williams-Verwoerd" (L6-9-7-117), September 1966; [86393-65]
        (Speaks of apartheid in South Africa)
        - Original:, 16mm film, color, pos, mag, 00:01:08
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 14)
        - Streaming File: 86393-65, flv
      - "Williams Operation" (L6-9-19-22), September 1966; [86393-66]
        (His son speaks of GMW's recent operation)
        - Original:, 16mm film, color, pos, mag, 00:00:43
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 14)
        - Streaming File: 86393-66, flv
      - "Mrs. Williams and Governor Williams' Health" (L6-9-24-43), September 1966; [86393-67]
        (Nancy Williams speaks about GMW's recent operation)
        - Original:, 16mm film, color, pos, mag, 00:01:14
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 14)
        - Streaming File: 86393-67, flv
      - "Williams News Conference" (L6-9-31-84), September 1966; [86393-68]
        (Speaks of possibility of President ? coming to Michigan to speak on Labor Day)
        - Original:, 16mm film, color, pos, mag, 00:00:32
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 14)
        - Streaming File: 86393-68, flv
      - "Williams-Politics" (L6-10-13-12), October 1966; [86393-69]
        (Post-operation interview about the campaign)
        - Original:, 16mm film, color, pos, mag, 00:00:57
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 14)
        - Streaming File: 86393-69, flv
      - "Williams Blasts Griffin" (L6-11-1-153), November 1966; [86393-70]
        (Interview outside auto ? plant)
        - Original:, 16mm film, color, pos, mag, 00:00:46
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 14)
        - Streaming File: 86393-70, flv
      - "Williams, Politics, Education" (L6-11-24-98), November 1966; [86393-71]
        - Original:, 16mm film, color, pos, mag, 00:00:37
        - Use Copy:, DVD (Box 14)